[
    {
        "question": "🐒👑",
        "answer": "孙悟空",
        "dialog": "俺老孙来也！"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌺🧍‍♀️🐟",
        "answer": "美人鱼",
        "dialog": "人类的东西啊？\n好，我来看看。"
    },
    {
        "question": "🥷🐢🐢🐢🐢",
        "answer": "忍者神龟",
        "dialog": "The most important \ntraits of a ninja are\nspeed, stealth and precision!"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕵️💊➞👶🏻",
        "answer": "柯南",
        "dialog": "真相只有一个"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌀🔥🦊",
        "answer": "漩涡鸣人",
        "dialog": "看我的S级忍术\n色诱术😻💃😻，\n这样你还能猜到吗？"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐸🧝🏼‍♂️😍🧝🏼‍♂️",
        "answer": "自来也",
        "dialog": "本大爷就是妙木山的蛤蟆仙人！\n谁污蔑我是好色仙人！"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔲❄️👸",
        "answer": "白雪公主",
        "dialog": "🪞魔镜魔镜告诉我\n谁是世界上最美丽的女人？"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍚👨‍🦳🐭",
        "answer": "米老鼠",
        "dialog": "To laugh yourself is \nto love yourself!"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍬👨‍🦳🦆",
        "answer": "唐老鸭",
        "dialog": "Happiness is the richest thing \nwe will ever own."
    },
    {
        "question": "🪡🐷🦸‍♂️",
        "answer": "蜘蛛侠",
        "dialog": "能力越大\n责任越大"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦇🦸🏽‍♂️",
        "answer": "蝙蝠侠",
        "dialog": "It’s not who you are underneath,\nit’s what you do that defines you."
    },
    {
        "question": "🧽👶",
        "answer": "海绵宝宝"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍒🍡",
        "answer": "樱桃小丸子",
        "dialog": "变成家庭主妇以后\n连梦想都不见了"
    },
    {
        "question": "🛻⚽️",
        "answer": "皮卡丘",
        "dialog": "皮卡～皮卡～丘"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧊❄️👸🏼",
        "answer": "艾尔莎",
        "dialog": "Let it go, let it go\nThat perfect girl is gone."
    },
    {
        "question": "🌙🇾🇪🐰",
        "answer": "月野兔",
        "dialog": "我要代表月亮惩罚你"
    },
    {
        "question": "🚛🚕🔄🤖",
        "answer": "变形金刚",
        "dialog": "汽车人，出发！"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍒🪵🌹🛣",
        "answer": "樱木花道",
        "dialog": "天才的字典里，\n没有不可能这三个字。"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐶🌌🍴",
        "answer": "犬夜叉",
        "dialog": "泣いてねえっっ！"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐰8️⃣🎼",
        "answer": "兔八哥",
        "dialog": "嘿，伙计"
    }
]